

# Tommaso Padovan Computer Scientist



5 July 1993



Rhönring 141 Darmstadt, 64289 Germany



+39 3484655214



tommaso.pado@gmail.com

## About me ——

Alice is a sensible prepubescent girl from a wealthy English family who finds herself in a strange world ruled by imagination and fantasy. Alice feels comfortable with her identity and has a strong sense that her environment is comprised of clear, logical, and consistent rules and features. Alice's familiarity with the world has led one critic to describe her as a "disembodied intellect". Alice displays great curiosity and attempts to fit her diverse experiences into a clear understanding of the world.

# Skills —

Java

polite

outgoing

good manners

pursuer of rabbits

### lovely\*4 narcissistic\*3

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

## Education

2017	Master degree (Erasmus) in Computer Science Specializing in Computer Vision, CUDA and Game Technology stadt" <sup>1</sup>	Darmstadt at "TU Darm-
2016	Master degree in Computer Science At "Università degli Studi di Padova" <sup>2</sup>	Padova (Italy)
2013-2016	Bachelor degree in Computer Science Achieved with 100/110 at "Università degli Studi di Padova" <sup>2</sup>	Padova (Italy)
2007-2012	High school  Lyceum of Sciences and Informatics	Treviso (Italy)

	Lyceum of Sciences and informatics			
Work Experience				
2016-2017	Developer at "Vision Lab Apps srl" <sup>3</sup> Android + back-end of streaming application for smartphon	Part-time Job es and glasses.		
2016	Developer at "Vic World Wide" <sup>4</sup> Prototype app for "world 3D reconstruction" using Google-Ton mobile devices.	Stage ango framework		
2015-2016	Developer at "EasyApp srl" <sup>5</sup> Front-end and back-end for ERPs.	Freelance Job		
IT Skills				

## Programming languages

Strong knowledge in procedural, object-oriented, concurrent, functional and actorbased programming paradigms.

Discreet experience with: Strong experience with:

• C++ • CUDA C++ Scala (and akka) Python Javascript/NodeJS Java aha Julia Haskell • Go

#### Tools and frameworks

- · Good practice with IDEs and frameworks as JetBrains Suite, QT, Android Studio, Laravel, etc.
- · Familiarity with Git/GitFlow both with CLI and graphical interfaces; basic understanding of Subversion and Mercurial.
- Teamwork experience acquired during academic and professional projects; good skills in using work management-tools such as teamwork.com, Trello, GanttProject, Slack, etc.
- Good knowledge of UML graphical language and UML-editors (e.g. Astah).
- Good knowledge of Google Tango<sup>6</sup> framework for augmented reality in mobile devices.

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>1</sup> https://www.informatik.tu-darmstadt.de

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>2</sup>http://www.unipd.it

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>3</sup>http://www.visionlabapps.com

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>4</sup>http://vicworldwide.com/it/your-eyes-worldwide

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>5</sup>http://www.easyappsrl.it

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>6</sup>https://developers.google.com/tango/